Summary of stress in two-word phrases. First word, set phrases, light bulb,
streets, main street, company or corporation, Xerox Corporation,
nationalities of food, Chinese food, nationalities of people, French guy.
Second word, descriptive phrases, new information, road designations, Fifth
Avenue, modified adjectives, really big, Place names and parks New York Central
Park Institutions or incorporated Oakland Museum Xerox, Inc. Personal names and
titles Bob Smith Assistant Manager Personal pronouns and possessives His car
Bob's brother Articles The bus A week An hour Initials and acronyms U.S. IQ
Chemical compounds Zinc oxide and numbers red orange 26 most compound verbs go away
sit down fall off percent and dollar ten percent fifty dollars hyphenated
nationalities african-american descriptive nationalities Mexican restaurant